KRIPKE:
Three different men?!
(Barry:)Damn, girl,
way to give the milk away?
(Amy:)Oh, looks like
we just lost Kripke.
Actually, I'm still here.
(Amy:)Now?
Yup.
Yup!
(Amy:)Now?
(Amy:)Oh, looks like
we just lost Kripke.
(Raj:)Before Emily,
I was alone for so long.
(Raj:)I just... I don't know
if I can do that again.
(Maitre d':)Well, you know,
here is something
(Sheldon:)that might cheer you up.
(Sheldon:)The flag of the Isle of Man
is nothing but three legs
(Sheldon:)sharing a weird pair
of underpants, so...
(Sheldon:)you think you
got problems.
(Amy:)I have an idea.
(Amy:)Maybe someone in our audience
(Amy:)would be interested
in meeting Rajesh.
(Amy:)Ladies, I can attest
(Amy:)that he is a kind,
handsome, intelligent...
KOOTHRAPPALI: Rich parents!
Don't forget, rich parents!
(Amy:)...spoiled astrophysicist
who not only...
(phone ringing)
(Amy:)Oh. Well, that was quick.